<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Nursing Home Care</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Nursing Home Care</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="about_us">Nursing Home Care About Us</string>


    <string name="about_subheading">Nursing Home Care BD Since 2012</string>
    <string name="about_paragraph">
        Nurse Service at home as a concept of home aide care began to develop in Bangladesh.
        In Asia, particularly Bangladesh, Health care provider is at a very new stage compared
        to developing countries.\n www.nursinghomecarebd.com \n
        Do you know, 60% of non-urgent medical care currently provided at the hospital can be done completely at home
        if you have a proper nursing service organization or senior care home?
        Indeed, Homecare or home-based health care is a solution that is increasingly
        suitable for our lifetime and elderly home care.
        Now, we are from Nursing Home Care are promised to provide Nurse Service at home facilities.
        As we believe long-lasting and meaningful relationships between home patients, their friends or families,
        and our house care team, we are delivering nursing
        home care service at home along with equipment service and medical diagnosis service.

    </string>

    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>


    <string name="privacy_paragraph">
        Conclusion:
        Through our nursing home care service, you will not feel alone or bored,
        which you feel in the hospital while taking treatment. This personalized
        approach helps build a trusting relationship between patients and care providers and ensures
        collaborative efforts for recovery. Our dedicated team of nurses or attendants is with you at every step,
        throughout your journey to provide a sense of security, comfort, and convenience. Our senior care service or
        older people home service has already in a standard position of patient care service in Dhaka. Regarding medical
        equipment rental service, you will get guaranteed medical equipment and facilities with free using system method.\n
        Our well-experienced employee will teach you how to use each equipment safely or when can they call again for a free assessment.
        Finally, being at home, our service ensures that you get the full attention of the care provider. Additionally,
        this helps in a better understanding of patient and family expectations that helps service providers anticipate
        upcoming problems, much faster than in hospitals. So if you are looking for nurse service at home in Dhaka bd,
        you can blindly trust NHC and book an appointment by today.
</string>


    <string name="term_and_condition">Term and Condition</string>


    <string name="term_paragraph">
        To improve lung failure, asthma, poisoning, COAD, severe bleeding, heart attack, shock, and cystic fibrosis oxygen cylinder used.
        Oxygen Cylinder is a high-pressure, non-reactive, and non-coating steel container for compressed gas (O2) that used for medical or diagnostic purposes.
        It also used for cardiovascular stability, resuscitation and helpful for artificially ventilated patients
</string>


    <string name="contract_paragraph">
       <b>Head Office:</b>\n
        House#1, Block#A, Word#6, Vatara,\n
        <b>Road:</b>Cholmohid kkhondokar barir more.
        Contact Number:<b>01719661366, 01714585817
        \n 01783656777, 01885553300</b>\n
        <b>Email:alimranrubel66@gmail.com</b>
        \n\nVisit our Website\n<b>www.nursinghomecarebd.com</b>

    </string>
    <string name="nurse_provide">
        <b>Nurse Service at home:</b>\n\n
        Our home service is ideal for patients who need long-term health care for complex medical problems
        and daily needs. This program aims to help elderly home patients regain their independence through
        a systematic and loving care plan specifically designed for each senior care.
        Our nursing home care offering experienced female and male attendants to our clients. All attendants,
        nurses are skilled and well-trained to serve our clients on time. We offer reliable and
        trustworthy staff and offer your complete security guarantee.
        We guarantee that all nurses are polite and registered with Bsc. Nursing degree and all attendants registered with a paramedic degree.
        Since our operations, we aim to meet every expectation of our clients our nursing home is called the best nursing homes support in Dhaka Bangladesh.
        www.nursinghomecarebd.com\n\n
        <b>We offers:</b>\n
        Male and female nurse service.
        Male and female attendant.
        Post-natal and new born baby care.
        Physiotherapy service.
        Postoperative care.\n\n
        Injection / vaccination on call.
        Male and female nurse service:
        Our professional home care services include a variety of care and support services for individuals who are recovering from hospital care,
        disabled, chronic, or seriously ill. We already know patients recover much better, and faster, at home because the risk of infection
        reduced and the chance of re-entry to the hospital minimized. Do you know who needs this service more?
        • Patients returning home after surgery require care, supervision, and assistance
        • Patients who undergo complicated treatments that require the use of medical equipment and drug monitoring
        • People suffering from chronic illnesses and disabilities, such as kidney disease, dementia, heart failure.\n
        https://www.facebook.com/NursingHomeCareBD/\n

</string>
    <string name="doctor_service">

                <b>Diagnosis or laboratory test service at home </b>\n\n
        The last category of nurse service we deliver at home is Medical dialysis service on call.
        Under this, we collect laboratory samples for different diseases from patients
        blood urine poop from their homes and provide 100%  correct test report to the patient on time.\n\n
        <b>Our test includes:</b>\n\n
        Complete Blood Picture\n
        Blood Sugar levels\n
        HbA1C levels\n
        Prothrombin time and INR\n
        Thyroid function tests\n
        Arterial blood gases-ABG\n
        Serum electrolytes\n
        Urinanalysis\n\n
        <b>Conclusion:</b>\n\n
        Through our nursing home care service, you will not feel alone or bored, which you feel in the hospital while taking treatment.
        This personalized approach helps build a trusting relationship between patients and care providers and ensures
        collaborative efforts for recovery. Our dedicated team of nurses or attendants is with you at every step,
        throughout your journey to provide a sense of security, comfort, and convenience. Our senior care service
        or older people home service has already in a standard position of patient care service in Dhaka.
        Regarding medical equipment rental service, you will get guaranteed medical equipment and facilities with free using system method.
        Our well-experienced employee will teach you how to use each equipment safely or when can they call again for a free assessment.
        Finally, being at home, our service ensures that you get the full attention of the care provider.
        Additionally, this helps in a better understanding of patient and
        family expectations that helps service providers anticipate upcoming problems, much faster than in hospitals.
        So if you are looking for nurse service at home in Dhaka bd, you can blindly trust NHC and book an appointment by today.
    </string>
    <string name="medical_equipment">
        <b>Medical equipment service at home:</b>\n\n
        We provide medical equipment’s for all client needs.
        The equipment’s offered by us are very reliable and well researched.
        We always carry out a background check on every equipment before using.
        Furthermore, equipment rental rates can be negotiated based on client budget constraints.
        We provide more experienced staff members based on the equipment system.
        The liability and reliability of the equipment provided by us are guaranteed including:\n\n

        Wheelchair\n
        Medical Beds\n
        Mattress/n
        Pulse Oximeter\n
        Suction apparatus\n
        Ventilator\n
        Syringe Pump\n\n

        Read More\n
        Visit Our Website:\n
        www.nursinghomecarebd.com


    </string>
    <string name="baby_care">

       <b> Post-natal and newborn baby care:</b>\n\n
        A new baby is undoubtedly a very pleasant time for everyone at home.
        But it is also true that a new mother experiences many physiological annd emotional changes,
        after the birth of a child. It is the time when a mother recovers from the birth of a child and
        requires expert attention and care for the baby and mother.
        By understanding the importance of postnatal care,\n\n
        we offer nurses or ayeas or female attendant.
        Our trained staff will advise you at every step to ensure you recover from the birth of your child,
        while your baby is cared for by experts in your own home environment. To care for babies,
        our nurses provide much-needed support for maintaining baths and general hygiene,
        massage, regular feeding, washing, support for mothers, babysitting, and so on.
        As far as caring for mothers, our nurses are trained to monitor all the problems
        and provide the necessary advice so that the mother can find out the problems that
        will occur in advance.\n


    </string>
    <string name="oxygen_service">

        <b>Medical equipment service at home:</b>\n\n
        We provide medical equipments for all client needs.
        The equipments offered by us are very reliable and well researched.
        We always carry out a background check on every equipment before using.
        Furthermore, equipment rental rates can be negotiated based on client budget constraints.
        We provide more experienced staff members based on the equipment system.
        The liability and reliability of the equipment provided by us are guaranteed including:\n\n
        Oxygen Cylinder\n
        Oxygen Concentrator\n\n

        <b>Oxygen Cylinder:</b>\n\n
        To improve lung failure, asthma, poisoning, COAD, severe bleeding,
        heart attack, shock, and cystic fibrosis oxygen cylinder used.
        Oxygen Cylinder is a high-pressure, non-reactive,
        and non coating steel container for compressed gas (O2)
        that used for medical or diagnostic purposes.
        It also used for cardiovascular stability, resuscitation and helpful for artificially
        ventilated patients
        Oxygen Concentrator\n\n
        Oxygen concentrator also allows patients to use<b>24/7</b>oxygen therapy,\n
        which helps increase their chances of survival in an emergency case.
        It also increases patients tolerance, stamina for daily exercise or activities,
        and increases metabolism. Its a device shaped.\n
        So, it does not have a filling or carrying problem.\n

    </string>
</resources>
